https://www.ictp.it/terms-of-use.aspx

Data Protection and Web Terms of UseData Protection
If you are a user of any of the ICTP online systems you can revoke the use of your data at any time. If you receive updates or news letters from us you can ask for them to be canceled. All of the data stored at the ICTP are used only for public and institutional purposes according to the aims of ICTP.
Should you have questions on this process or any request regarding your personal data please contact the ICTP at data-protection@ictp.it
Web Terms of Use
IdentityThe use of the name, acronym, logo and/or domain name of ICTP must be expressly authorized in advance and in writing, and must comply with the specified conditions and procedures, in particular with respect to its visual presentation, duration and scope.
PermissionsICTP exercises copyright over its information to assure its proper use in accordance with the Centre's principles. Any copy made of the material must retain all copyright and other proprietary legends and notices in the same form and manner as on the original. Any use of textual and multimedia information (sound, image, software, etc.) in the website shall be accompanied by an acknowledgement of the source, citing the uniform resource locator (URL) of the page (Title of the material, © ICTP, URL).
PrivacyBy accessing the ICTP website, certain information, such as Internet protocol (IP) addresses, navigation behaviour through the website, the software used and the time spent, along with other similar information, will be stored on servers. These will not specifically identify you. The information will be used internally only for website traffic analysis. If you provide unique identifying information, such as name, email address, postal address and other information on forms stored on this website, such information will be used only for statistical purposes and will not be published for general access nor disclosed or sold to third parties. ICTP, however, assumes no responsibility for the security of this information.
DisclaimerICTP does not warrant that the information, documents and materials contained in its website is complete and correct and shall not be liable whatsoever for any damages incurred as a result of its use.
Linking to ICTPAny external website may provide a hyperlink to the ICTP portal or any of its pages without requesting permission. However, this must not infringe ICTP's intellectual property rights in particular relating to its name, logo, copyright or author's rights. The ICTP logo may not be used in providing a hyperlink unless specifically authorized by mutual agreement or partnership. Hyperlinks to the ICTP portal should point to the ICTP homepage - www.ictp.it - or to major thematic sections. Deeper links should be avoided, as ICTP cannot guarantee their longevity.
Links from the ICTP websiteHyperlinks to other websites imply neither responsibility for, nor approval of, the information, documents and materials contained in those other websites on the part of ICTP. These Hyperlinks should not be construed as an endorsement by ICTP of the validity, accuracy or views expressed in those other websites.
Cookie policy
Information note pursuant to Art. 13 of the Decrete n. 196/2003 (also called Privacy Code)
The present information note has been published is compliance with the dispositions of Art.122 of Decrete n.196/2003 and the Decision 229/2014 of the Garante per la Protezione dei Dati Personali regarding cookies.
Users’ Personal Information, registered or not, may be collected by cookies.
What are cookies?
Cookies are small text files that are sent to the user's terminal equipment by visited websites; they are stored in the user's terminal equipment to be then re-transmitted to the websites on the user's subsequent visits to those websites.
Technical Cookies are used as basic and essential tool for the execution of specific functional services for the improvement of single aspects of the website.
Types of Cookies:
Technical Cookies are strictly necessary for navigation and for the correct functioning of the website.
Functional Cookies allow users to navigate as a function of certain pre-determined criteria (e.g. language) so as to improve the quality of service.
Analytical Cookies allow to recognize and collect aggregate information on the number of visitors and the pattern of visits to the website. Analytical cookies are assimilated to technical cookies and are used directly by the website first party to improve their usability.
Profiling Cookies are aimed at creating user profiles and they are used to send advertising messages to the user’s device, in line with the preferences shown by the user during navigation. Because of the highly invasive nature of these cookies in the user’s private sphere, Italian and European legislation requires users to be informed appropriately on their use so as to give their valid consent.
Pursuant to article 122 of the Privacy Code (Personal Data Protection Code), data subject’s consent for technical cookies is not required, but this policy is sufficient  as their use is limited to the technical storage or the access to already stored information, in fact technical cookies are used exclusively with a view to "carrying out the transmission of a communication on an electronic communications network, or insofar as this is strictly necessary to the provider of an information society service that has been explicitly requested by the contracting party or user to provide the said service."
First-Party Cookies and Third-Party Cookies
By using this website, analytics or technical and profiling cookies can be installed on the user’s device, and they can be distinguished in First-Party (the manager of the website that the user is visiting, also called Publisher) and Third-Party Cookies, pursuant to decision n.229/2014. Regarding these last ones, it is important to underline that Third-Party could modify features and functions of cookies, independently from the Publisher’s will. In fact, by installing these cookies, the Publisher is a mere technical mediator
Google Analytics
These cookies are used to collect aggregate information on the number of visitors and the pattern of visits to the website. They see how visitors move around the website when they are using it and to record which content viewers view and are interested in, helping the Publisher to improve the service and the functioning of the website (e.g. visited pages, errors tat may occur, count of visitors that are using the web services, in order to improve the web experience and the navigation speed).
Those cookies are managed by Google Analytics, a web analytics tool provided by Google Inc. For instance, some Google Analytics’ cookies are:
__utmz; __utmc; __utmb; __utma; __utmt.
To get more information about these cookies, please visit: https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage.
Pursuant to Decision 229/2014, technical tools are adopted in order to reduce the identifying power of these cookies. Google Privacy Policy is available at https://www.google.com/intl/it/policies/privacy/, whereas Google Analytics Privacy information is available at https://support.google.com/analytics/topic/2919631?hl=it&ref_topic=1008008.
Third-Party Cookies could be set and modified by different organisation to the owner of the website, therefore ICTP is not responsible for later modifications and integrations to Third-Party Cookies information note and for variations to their functions.
How to disable cookies and manage preferences
Most browsers allow cookies to be checked, accepted, or even disabled, cookies using browser settings. It is important to note that disabling technical cookies can compromise the proper functioning of the website and lose user profiles’ information and preferences.
The links for specific instructions of the most popular browsers are listed below:
Firefox:  https://support.mozilla.org/it/kb/Attivare%20e%20disattivare%20i%20cookie
Chrome: https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=it-IT&hlrm=fr&hlrm=en
Internet Explorer: http://windows.microsoft.com/it-it/windows7/block-enable-or-allow-cookies
Safari: https://support.apple.com/kb/PH19214?locale=it_IT
Moreover, here below the link to disable analytical cookies of Google Analitycs: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=it
ICTP is governed by UNESCO, IAEA, and Italy, and is a UNESCO Category 1 Institute
ICTP is governed by UNESCO, IAEA, and Italy, and is a UNESCO Category 1 Institute
CheckRedirectPage
http://library.ictp.it/ejds.aspx
